<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0">
    <channel>
        <title><![CDATA[All things art and entertainment in: Film, Games, Literature, et al]]></title>
        <description><![CDATA[All things art and entertainment in: Film, Games, Literature, et al]]></description>
        <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/</link>
        <generator>The Grid</generator>
        <lastBuildDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 09:32:47 GMT</lastBuildDate>
        <atom:link href="https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/rss.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Main site]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Main site</h1><p>You can find me at the following:</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/main-site/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">c063b5b6-c5b3-46b4-a0d2-10e5fef02aec</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 09:32:43 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Life is Strange (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Life is Strange (2015)</h1><h2>Episode 1</h2><p>I'll start at the end.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/life-is-strange-2015/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">3bb16be7-0674-4185-81e8-3c60d90449d5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sat, 07 May 2016 09:30:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Firewatch (2016)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Firewatch (2016)</h1><p>We first started hearing about Firewatch a couple of years back, and while some of the heritage of Campo studio is familiar (Staff worked, Bioshock 2, The Walking Dead and Ninja Blade), this is their first title as a new studio. It shouldn't be surprising to hear, that as a high-er profile Indie title, there's a PS4 version and the game is built with Unity. Undoubtedly, the visuals sing brighter than many Unity games achieve (Homeworld: Deserts of Kharak looked very "Unity", perhaps because comparison with its brother and sister are easy), with a colour palette that makes the world shine with strong bright colours, crisp shadows and warm light. As the sun shifts across the landscape, while mist traces along a cold creek in the early morning, there's much to celebrate in the game art, and nature itself.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/firewatch-2016/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">21323b3c-5e4e-4843-ac0d-6b0ef5266cbb</guid>
            <pubDate>Tue, 03 May 2016 20:04:00 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Code Name: STEAM (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Code Name: STEAM (2015)</h1><p>As is a tendency of anyone when attempting to describe a videogame, and to give it life through words, we tend to make parallels. The pedigree behind STEAM includes Advance Wars and Fire Emblem, and the chessboard like structure to the strategy world clearly mirrors that heritage. In addition, we have a heavy dose of Valkyria Chronicles, both in terms of hypothetically historic settings and those glorious cell shaded visuals that help the titles sing, rendered in a reality of their own making. But there's more. Your foes are a set of aliens and your weapons and the worlds are powered by some kind of elaborate Steampunk (hence the name) and the story bubbles along like an exaggerated 60s American comic.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/code-name-steam-2015/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">59d65d2c-c37f-4f49-8004-b80f308556fd</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:51:19 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Whiplash - 2014]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Whiplash - 2014</h1><p>A film about Jazz doesn't jump to the top of many people's lists of must see films. But that overwhelming focus on perfection, both in expectation and personal desire, translates across any medium, whether music, sportsmanship or almost anything else. There's more than a sense of a drill sergeant from Simmons's character - Fletcher - as he barks out obscenities and attacks each member of his band. His, is definitely the stand out performance, with an incredible range of anger on show from patient frustration (during a first time practice) through to bombastic rage in a matter of moments... Simmons never misses a beat.</p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/whiplash-2014/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">bd33e324-9f07-4a9f-aa6c-bbb12e62ea19</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:38:45 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Witch (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Witch (2015)</h1><p>I find jump scares scary. But I don't find them fun. Well done everyone, you got me! The intense orchestra, the clever editing and the make-up / cgi department all came together, and I got scared... Round of applause</p><img src="https://s3-us-west-2.amazonaws.com/the-grid-img/p/a504e051a1a20f2e749b8ec96f674e3381c26cbc.jpg"></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thefilmqueuedotcom.files.wordpress.com/2016/02/the-witch-movie-2016-film-wallpaper-hd-exclusive-goat.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">0bfc7131-adc7-480a-904d-4cd9dc082eb3</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:38:31 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Ant-Man (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>Ant-Man (2015)</h1><p>It is interesting, seeing a film and getting the feeling it wasn't meant to be. Not in terms of its quality or a stroke of luck from fate. With Ant-Man, we have a full on mockery of every super hero trope there is, wrapped in the narrative of a classic comic book film. From the outset, let's be clear and highlight that the film pulls plenty of punches. Especially early on, this is ticking a list of check boxes with almost indifference. We meet the hero (Stan) and meet his family, finding both his opportunity for redemption and his reason to fight the powers of evil… or rather to rob the rich. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/ant-man-2015/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">103c00c6-4827-4c96-bca5-f03326723977</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:32:11 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[The Fisher King (1991)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<article><h1>The Fisher King (1991)</h1><p>It's odd trying not to admit that a 23 year old film has become dated. It was 1991, and the world wasn't sure what the 90's would be yet. Tape records, a heavy focus on the radio and newspapers, and a soundtrack that certainly plucks a little harder at the minds distant memories than one would like to admit, all stand together to make it clear, you are watching an old film of yester year and times have changed. It's interesting then, when originality can flow so easily and readily from a Hollywood piece. Robin Williams and Jeff Bridges are both well-established actors by this time, and it's hardly Terry Gilliam's first film. But you can't imagine a more appropriately cast and well thought through alternative romp. </p></article>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/the-fisher-king-1991/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">4f9bbf3f-e690-41f1-a0f9-324979492898</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:23:23 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Steve Jobs (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<p>As time marches on, the meaning and value of Steve Jobs continues to shift. Now part of legend, popular culture has started to echo the back lash against Steve for headlining the credits of multiple devices - that owed more to those around him than Jobs himself. All the while, main stream media continues to try to digest this realist view of the man, along with the IT rock star image that it built around him. Though harder to make a visual connection between Steve and Fassbender, this latest effort, is undoubtedly a more successful film than the other recent namesake "Jobs" 2013. In fact, that lack of "cosmetic puppetry" assists the film's earnestness as a character piece - questioning motive and art all the while... But let's return to the nuts and bolts of the movie.</p>]]></description>
            <link>https://thegrid.ai/state-of-the-media/steve-jobs-2015/index.html</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">2fa143af-74d6-46f8-9842-b9a7a5fb84f5</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:03:47 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
        <item>
            <title><![CDATA[Parasite I & II (2015)]]></title>
            <description><![CDATA[<img src="http://asianmoviepulse.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/post/parasyte-part-1-2014-review/shinichi-migi-parasyte1.jpg">]]></description>
            <link>http://asianmoviepulse.com/wp-content/uploads/2015/01/post/parasyte-part-1-2014-review/shinichi-migi-parasyte1.jpg</link>
            <guid isPermaLink="false">314417cd-302d-4085-953a-afd6a2bd7b0b</guid>
            <pubDate>Sun, 01 May 2016 18:01:51 GMT</pubDate>
        </item>
    </channel>
</rss>